Tip number one, for determining your signature scent.
Number one, start by going to your local bookstore or newsstand and picking up a whole bunch of magazines.
Fashion magazines are the best place to find perfume samples.
For men, choose Details and Esquire.
Magazines like that will have men oriented perfumes.
For women, any kind of magazine.
Vogue, El, Etc.
will all have plenty of women oriented perfume samples.
Once you've got the magazine and make sure you buy them.
Because, newsstands don't take kindly to people tearing out their samples on the street.
Pick through the magazine and flip through to try and find as many perfume samples as you can.
Once you've found as many as you can, tear them all out.
And, open them each up individually.
Begin, by just smelling the page.
And, then if you like you can run the perfume sample onto your wrist behind your ear or anywhere else where your body tends to get warm.
This will help you determine, if you like the perfume on your body.